

ALEX LEWIS

GRAPHIC DESIGNER / FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Address:

1641 Patterson Rd Smiths Grove, KY 42171

Phone: (270) 799-5591, E-mail: alex.lewis@gmail.com Website: skymx99.github.io

SUMMARY

A junior Full Stack Developer with experience working with various web development technologies and mobile app creation. Well versed in front-end / back-end development, and graphic design creating a unique set of skills that bridge the gap between designers and programmers.

PROJECTS

React Native: Developed a native app for iOS and Android using the Agile methodology in a team environment. The app utilized many native components that allows users to sign up, create a profile, access the device camera, post photo's and share images with friends based on locations around specific sites across a city.

Game Development: Currently developing a video game for PC and Mac platforms using Unity3d.

Motocross: Chasing the Dream will be available in 2019.

SKILLS

HTML5	
CSS3	
JavaScript	
React	
BootStrap	
Node.js	
MySQL	
jQuery	
3D Modeling	
Unity3d	
Adobe Photoshop	
Adobe Illustrator	
Adobe XD	
Adobe Animate	

STRENGTHS

Creativity	
Reliability	
Communication	
Leadership	

EXPERIENCE

Dec. 2016 - Sept. 2017

Associate Product Engineer

FRUIT OF THE LOOM

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Assisted in development for wide range of safety equipment and apparel
- Utilized SolidWorks CAD software in development of new products
- Maintained Database of all garments style info and decoration placements
- Organized and scheduled fit sessions to ensure proper fit and make changes when necessary

Mar. 2014 - Sept. 2015

Merchandising Systems Associate

FRUIT OF THE LOOM

responsibilities:

- Transformed production artwork into vector product mock-ups
- Collaborated with Programming Team to expand online presence
- Created easy to understand technical documents
- Spearheaded the development for dynamic 3D product configuration

Aug. 2007 - Mar. 2014

Lab Manager / Senior Photographer

ALLSTAR PHOTOGRAPHY

RESPONSIBILITIES

- ■Inventory, product design, staffing, equipment maintenance, and training
- Supervised teams of event coordinators, photographers, and assistants
- Designed all products including plaques, posters, and sublimated products
- Implemented QR Code scanning for an order entry system

Apr. 2006 - Dec. 2006

Associate Level Designer

RAINBOW STUDIOS

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Created 3D terrains and race tracks based on input from the design team
- Participated in brainstorming meetings, blueprints, design, and beta testing
- Served as model motocross rider for various audio recordings
- Moderated company message board to provide product information

EDUCATION

2011

Western Kentucky University

SKILLS ACQUIREL

B.S. Systems Management

an. 2018 - Mar. 2018

Covalence Coding Bootcamp

SKILLS ACQUIRED

Full Stack Development Certification Experience building web applications, mobile apps, databases, and backend APIs